{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"8.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"T. Engeldrum","title":"SOLQ Liaison Training (Online Version)","description":"project description","email":"engeldrumt@hra.nyc.gov","website":"","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":34062,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":21,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si5468","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","title":"Understanding your resposibilities as a Liaison for the SOLQ System in Solving Exceptions by Users at your particular Site. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_1","title":"Remote SOLQ Liaison Training ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"This training presentation has been developed to be remotely accessed by prospective SOLQ Liaisons, authorized by their RA/RC SOLQ Contacts, thru management, to act as a Liaison.  SOLQ Liaisons represent, and are extensions of, the SOLQ Auditor and Administrator for a particular predefined area of responsibility for SOLQ Users in the Department of Social Services for the City of New York.  These predifined areas of responsibility are referred to as “SOLQ Sites.”   This training presentation has been designed to meet the stringent requirements for SOLQ utilization and exception resolution as defined by New York State.  It should be utilized in conjunction with the other learning materials provided and the SOLQ Use and Resolution procedure.  You can control the pace of the presentation by utilizing the controls at the bottom of the panel.  Thank you.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4714","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":450},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4714"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_22","title":"SOLQ Liaison Training Layout ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"Slide Presentation (Process & Reposibilities) Video Demonstration (Accessing & Solving) Quick Quiz SOLQ Links ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"The presentation will take aproximately 15 - 20 minutes to complete. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13465","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_76","Text_Caption_79"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":450},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13465"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_4","title":"Information to Know ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"The SOLQ Auditor & Administrator for NYC is the Office of Data Security Management (ODSM). They can be reached at datasecurity@dss.nyc.gov ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9237","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":360},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9237"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_2","title":"Process... ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"When a User triggers an exception in the SOLQ application, their name, User ID and additional information appears on a monthly report generated by New York State (exception report). ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"This information is loaded into SOLQ SharePoint where it is sub-divided by Site. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"SOLQ SharePoint automatically generates an email with the subject: SOLQ Exception Reported - Action Required. This notifies the SOLQ Liaison that exceptions have been generated by Users at their particular Site and that an action is required. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide8872","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_5","Text_Caption_6","Text_Caption_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":915},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8872"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_9","title":"Process... ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Once in SOLQ SharePoint, the Liaison(s) will see a list of exceptions generated by Users at their particular Site for a particular time period. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"The Liaison(s) will now investigate each exception from their Site; will attest to the legitimacy of...or report on a violation of use. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"The SOLQ Liaison will access SOLQ SharePoint thru the link provided in the body of the email. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9656","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_25","Text_Caption_26","Text_Caption_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":780},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9656"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_5","title":"Exceptions & Liaisons: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"Exceptions must be “solved” within twelve days of receipt of the original email notification.  Failure to do so could result in the suspension of SOLQ User rights at that Site. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"An exception is considered “solved” if it has been determined that the query was actuated for “legitimate business purposes” and a reason is provided for the search or if it is determined that the query was performed for non-valid reasons and then reported upon. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide9278","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_13","Text_Caption_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":930},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9278"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_11","title":"Exceptions & Liaisons: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"The exception report is produced on the tenth day of every month (excluding weekends and holidays) and represents exceptions created during the full month that immediately preceeds the last completed calendar month before the report is generated.  For Example: a May 10th report is for March exceptions. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"If an exception contiues to be left incomplete, MIS Data Security is notified.  Security will continue notification escalations thru proper channels until all exceptions are resolved. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9816","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_33","Text_Caption_84"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":720},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9816"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_12","title":"Exceptions & Liaisons: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"Liaisons must assure that each exception (flagged query) generated at their Site was initiated while utilizing the system for “legitimate business purposes” or report it as a violation of use.  They can conclude this by: matching the exception with a case (electronically or manually); physically discussing it with the User; any means at their disposal. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"Each SOLQ Site should be represented by two Liaisons.  Because of the time constraints involved in “solving” exceptions, each Liaison at a Site can solve any exception at their Site within twelve days of receipt of original email. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9989","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_37","Text_Caption_83"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":840},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9989"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_13","title":"Exceptions & Liaisons: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"If the Liaison discovers that an exception was created for non-legitimate reasons, that is, for purposes not related to the proper administration of DSS programs, the Liaison will immediately notify the SOLQ Administrator of the infraction. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"By “solving” an exception, the Site Liaison is only assuring that the flagged query in question was actuated for “legitimate business purposes” or reporting on a violation. They do not need to figure out why the query was flagged. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10063","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_39","Text_Caption_82"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":750},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10063"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_14","title":"Other Liaison Resposibilities: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Timely notify the SOLQ Administrator (via email at datasecurity@dss.nyc.gov) of any changes in the status of a SOLQ User or Liaison at my Site that would affect the eligibility of the User to continue to use SOLQ or the Liaison to continue to fulfill their duties (such changes include but are not limited to transfers, change in duties, retirement, termination, and extended medical leave). ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Work with the SOLQ Administrator to help facilitate changes in Site layout (i.e.  closing of a Site/ restructuring of a Site) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10133","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_40","Text_Caption_41"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1050},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10133"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"Accessing SOLQ SharePoint & Solving Exceptions ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"The following video demonstration will take you thru the steps from receiving an exception email notification through to the solving of the exception and then to the recording of the results of your investigation. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide10277","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_45","Text_Caption_46"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10277"}}},{"id":"Slide10387","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":12837},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10387"}}},{"id":"Button_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_16","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide10838","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":12810},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10838"}}},{"id":"si11681","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11671q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11815","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si11713","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11720","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What is a SOLQ Site? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11727","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si11735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11739","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A logical breakdown of SOLQ Users easily administered by a SOLQ Liaison(s). ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11735_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A logical breakdown of SOLQ Users easily administered by a SOLQ Liaison(s).\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11750","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Any group of SOLQ Users. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11746_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Any group of SOLQ Users.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11811","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si11819","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11671q0","for":"Slide11671q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11754","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11671q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11773","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Try Again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11671q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11792","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11671q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si11713","si11720","si11739","si11750","si11819","si11792"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11671"},"question":{"interactionId":"11700","quizId":469,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si12189","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12188q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12160","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","roles":{}},{"id":"si12010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","roles":{}},{"id":"si12022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"As Liaison for a SOLQ Site, you are required to solve exceptions for your Site within how many days of receipt of the email notification? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{}},{"id":"si12045","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"Six ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12045_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"5","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12060","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"Twelve  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12056_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twelve \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12188q1","for":"Slide12188q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12096","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12188q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"Incorrect - Try Again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12188q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12154","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12188q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12188","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si12022","si12034","si12049","si12060","si12178","si12154"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12188"},"question":{"interactionId":"12002","quizId":469,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"As Liaison for a SOLQ Site, you are required to solve exceptions for your Site within how many days of receipt of the email notification?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si12406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12405q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12377","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","roles":{}},{"id":"si12227","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","roles":{}},{"id":"si12239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12251","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"When solving an exception, you are required to figure out  what caused the exception? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"9","roles":{}},{"id":"si12262","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"No, you only have to assure the SOLQ Administrator that the exception was actuated while utilizing the system for “legitimate business purposes” or it was a violation of use. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12262_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, you only have to assure the SOLQ Administrator that the exception was actuated while utilizing the system for “legitimate business purposes” or it was a violation of use.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12273","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"Yes, the SOLQ Administrator must know what caused the exception. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12273_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12405q2","for":"Slide12405q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12313","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12405q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"Incorrect - Try Again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12405q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12405q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12405","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si12239","si12251","si12266","si12277","si12395","si12371"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12405"},"question":{"interactionId":"12219","quizId":469,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"As Liaison for a SOLQ Site, you are required to solve exceptions for your Site within how many days of receipt of the email notification?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si12638","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12637q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","roles":{}},{"id":"si12471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"Can an exception be solved without actually talking to the  User that created it? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12516","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"14","roles":{}},{"id":"si12494","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12498","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"Yes, if you have access to software (POS, etc.) that can verify that the the User was working on a particular case at the date and time specified in the exception. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12494_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, you only have to assure the SOLQ Administrator that the exception was actuated while utilizing the system for “legitimate business purposes” or it was a violation of use.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12505","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12509","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"No, you must always talk with the User to verify. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12505_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12637q3","for":"Slide12637q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12545","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12637q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Incorrect - Try Again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12637q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12637q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12637","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si12471","si12483","si12498","si12509","si12627","si12603"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12637"},"question":{"interactionId":"12451","quizId":469,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"As Liaison for a SOLQ Site, you are required to solve exceptions for your Site within how many days of receipt of the email notification?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si12855","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12854q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12826","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","roles":{}},{"id":"si12676","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","roles":{}},{"id":"si12688","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12700","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"Improper use of the SOLQ system includes: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12733","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19","roles":{}},{"id":"si12711","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"Accessing the system for a co-worker with a legitimate business purpose and logging that co-worker’s name, reason for the search and case number in the freeform field. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12711_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, you only have to assure the SOLQ Administrator that the exception was actuated while utilizing the system for “legitimate business purposes” or it was a violation of use.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12722","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"Utilizing the system to access information on a friend, co-worker, relative, yourself... ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12722_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Utilizing the system to access information on a friend, co-worker, relative, yourself...\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12844","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12854q4","for":"Slide12854q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12762","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12854q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12791","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"Incorrect - Try Again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12854q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12854q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12854","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si12688","si12700","si12715","si12726","si12844","si12820"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12854"},"question":{"interactionId":"12668","quizId":469,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"As Liaison for a SOLQ Site, you are required to solve exceptions for your Site within how many days of receipt of the email notification?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si13072","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13071q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","roles":{}},{"id":"si12893","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","roles":{}},{"id":"si12905","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12917","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"When non-legitimate use of the system is discovered, as Liaison, you should?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12950","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"24","roles":{}},{"id":"si12928","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12932","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"Cover-up for your co-worker and risk administrative, civil, and / or criminal charges. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, you only have to assure the SOLQ Administrator that the exception was actuated while utilizing the system for “legitimate business purposes” or it was a violation of use.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12939","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12943","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"Click the “Not Authorized/ODSM Escalation” radio button and explain the infraction in the Approver Notes field. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12939_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Utilizing the system to access information on a friend, co-worker, relative, yourself...\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13061","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13071q5","for":"Slide13071q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"Correct - Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13071q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"Incorrect - Try Again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13071q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13071q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13071","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si12905","si12917","si12932","si12943","si13061","si13037"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13071"},"question":{"interactionId":"12885","quizId":469,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"As Liaison for a SOLQ Site, you are required to solve exceptions for your Site within how many days of receipt of the email notification?\r","type":0,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si11885","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11928","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si11936","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si11901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quick Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11956","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si11960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11974","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11875","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11875"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_21","title":"SOLQ Links ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"SOLQ Liaison Guide ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"SOLQ Forms ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Animation_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Animation_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"The SOLQ Auditor & Administrator for NYC is the Office of Data Security Management (ODSM). They can be reached at datasecurity@dss.nyc.gov ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"SOLQ Liaison Agreement ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"SOLQ Use & Resolution Proceedure ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13134","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_73","Text_Caption_75","Text_Caption_78","Text_Caption_80","Text_Caption_81"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":450},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13134"}}},{"id":"SOLQ Liaison (HTML5)","class":"project","title":"SOLQ Liaison (HTML5)","children":["Slide4714","Slide13465","Slide9237","Slide8872","Slide9656","Slide9278","Slide9816","Slide9989","Slide10063","Slide10133","Slide10277","Slide10387","Slide10838","Slide11671","Slide12188","Slide12405","Slide12637","Slide12854","Slide13071","Slide11875","Slide13134"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":469,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide11671q0","Slide12188q1","Slide12405q2","Slide12637q3","Slide12854q4","Slide13071q5"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4714","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide13465","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide9237","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide8872","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide9656","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide9278","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide9816","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide9989","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide10063","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide10133","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide10277","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide10387","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide10838","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide11671","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide12188","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide12405","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide12637","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide12854","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide13071","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide11875","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide13134","title":"Slide 21"}]}